sup everyone Tim was only 50 with a very
special video today I'm proudly now it's
stiff finally finally you can donate to
the project the legend prophecy of Lion
darkness the power to save the world and
depending on how much money you donate
you get prizes I see you naab [ __ ]
check out this piece of ass people who
pledged to eat off get my completed my
racing and that's just the beginning
now originally I was going to use
Kickstarter however I found that patreon
is more user friendly and just just it
all looks better in my opinion like it
just looks cool look at all this [ __ ]
one oh my God now as I was saying on
this website you can actually learn
about the cows in the interesting story
learn about the world before you enter
now back to India back to the patronym
depend on how much money you donate you
can unlock special prizes and perks the
others do not get for example you can
donate any amount as I said I get every
little bit helps
I mean this [ __ ] isn't free I'm spending
time and money on this [ __ ] but hey I
love what I do so let's get stop for
example touch three dolls you get my
clear moderation go down tymberlee five
seven fan $10 or more people who pledge
$10 will receive the diesel download of
the game upon release pretty good deal
if you ask me I mean better than shot
off into a morass boom I mean I'm not
having mu box I can't put it out do you
see mu box in the [ __ ] was the [ __ ]
loop box all the way I don't got no
[ __ ] I don't do that I don't do that
[ __ ] I think people should get what they
pay for sometimes even free argue a [ __ ]
people pledge - we'll see video demo
game apart and the name will appear in
the credits as a special things by yours
truly
sup huge team and Fanfan spent 35 or
more war ced so down of the game a
Pollux and the name will appear in the
end credits block the previous one now
this you will gain to the good [ __ ] the
stuff that you really want to happen at
least that's what I believe
boom people place because we'll see this
is our game and the name appear in the
credits and they will get a digital
holiday eke out job by 2:35 I greet you
for the holidays sounds like a good deal
if you ask me to tears fam get the game
name the credits dizzy ecard boom
[ __ ] puts up one hard all us all that
good [ __ ] and you get to design in
overworld NPC you can be in the game for
just a hundred bucks you can be in my
game it's that not a steal moving down
150 bucks
goal terrify fan let's see think I can
reach this [ __ ] boom oh my God
you get designed in ingame boss that's
right you can be in the [ __ ] game you
can get your ass kicked
people pledged 200 bucks all this good
[ __ ] and you get inside a main character
who have a roid the [ __ ] stealing
just imagine how cool that be you get to
go on a journey with the main characters
of the game I mean [ __ ] just imagine
imagine everyone doing this she we can't
like have an army and [ __ ] of fighting
against the main villain Imagi cool that
would be I mean come on now this is even
the best [ __ ] you can actually get
better [ __ ] than that yeah [ __ ] we'll
check it out right now
oh my God donate a thousand bucks you
get to play the game a week before
anyone else
holy [ __ ] fifteen thousand bucks
you get everything [ __ ] Simon
character wants to it you get to play
the game two weeks two [ __ ] weeks for
everyone else oh my God holy [ __ ]
just imagine everyone I imagine being
the first person ever besides me of
course to play the [ __ ] game just
imagine how much better you're feel than
everyone else
oh my God this could all be yours this
could all be yours if you'd help donate
to the project I'm really excited to go
on this journey with you all hope you
guys are too I couldn't do this without
you
thanks [ __ ] ten to the five